uh few people have been asking about
starlink uh and what's up with that uh
regarding the whole you know road trip
thing so three days ago my
starlink suggested uh shipping date
passed and it been two weeks so I
ordered it uh on the 4th I think and I
sent I opened a support ticket and they
said uh I can read the email to you but
they said that because of you know
unlimited uh let's see because they're
out of
stock that they're waiting they're
waiting on delivery of new
items so they are hey thank you for
that so they're they're actually waiting
for they're sitting around waiting for
more devices to come according to the
support ticket and they they gave me a
$250 credit which makes sense because
they already took $2,700 from me
and they decided to take it now now I
did a lot of research online and there
are a number of people in different
forums that suggest the best way to do
this is to cancel your account but it's
also risky so here are the options by
the way if you're thinking of doing the
starlink thing let me just tell you the
options at up front so maybe this will
inform you if you're thinking about
doing the digital Nomad thing um a lot
of people are watching how this works
out and and I actually put that in my
ticket I put look this is a monumentally
market marketing opportunity for you uh
to let people know you know that that
I'm doing the Starling thing and and uh
I'm not asking for special treatment I
just want to you know to make sure stuff
works so so I'm going to summarize my
experience with Starling so far and
hopefully that'll help a couple of you
so the the again to recap I I ordered
about three weeks ago two and a half
three weeks ago and I was like okay fine
and it said preparing they took all my
money 2700 uh I got the high performance
one because the the other ones are not
worth it they're just not they're not
worth it especially if you're going to
do any kind of movement um I did find
out that the that the the Rome the Rome
dish uh which you can get a high
performance dish board if you want but
the Rome service um allows you to move
up to 10 miles an hour uh which means
that if you're if you're actually
walking you're good to go with that
particular service um if that's the one
you want but end up getting the mobile
priority which is $2,700 up front for a
high performance dish that plat high
performance plat dish which is required
and then you need mobile priority and
that gives you 40 gigabytes the 250
bucks a month gives you 40 gigabytes of
priority which is apparently you know
just prioritize data I made really
triple sure well I'll tell you for sure
but I I made a lot of um I did a lot of
checking with to to read the P print and
everything and read a bunch of forum
posts about it to make sure that
the um that the data is unlimited that
is the only reason I'm getting a
starling it is other than the obviously
the reason the remote reason the number
two major reason is because because it's
unlimited data and so somebody like me
that needs to be able to work from home
and stuff I don't need really high
speeds I just need really high
reliability and I need unlimited data on
the road I I don't have that with
Verizon Verizon runs out at 100 gigabits
and then they throttle you back to 600
so appar apparently um the non priority
data speeds are still something like 10
megabits per second 10 or 20 megabits
per second they're still better than any
hotel that you would ever stay in or any
Pub uh most people's like regular Wi-Fi
is it the same as my 100 100 megabits at
home my you know gigabit Ethernet my G
my fiber connection at home no it's not
the same as that and I will do another
video about that this this stream is
coming to you from it's going through my
home OBS um I decided to do that to save
money hey I'm Barney and hey Bellum so
the takeaway is that um Starling still
seems to be the right way to go uh my I
did get my mag mounts so that my
Starling can be mounted to the top of my
car and I will be routing um I decided
not to cut a hole in my roof so I'm
going to attempt to Route the wire
through the sunroof I'm going to crack
the sunroof um in a way that allows the
wire to come in um I do not have enough
clearance on my doors uh to let the wire
be shut in the door it will actually
probably wear out the wire and I did
read a lot of people say don't do that
it'll wear a wire out within a year and
it's hard to get replacement wires so so
I am going to hey there's a
fly there's a fly who got stuck because
of the net that's nice all right anyway
so so that's that's my plan um most of
the time my sunre is going to be open
anyway even when I'm driving driving so
I figure that's the way to go um the
only downside of that is water um I
haven't figured out what to do if and
when there's
water I I don't know if if it comes to
it I might there's a hole back here I
might there's a hole in the roof right
above my head right here I might go
ahead and just drill through the metal
there and just it all up because my
subar has already been kind of messed up
I mean it's my subar is on its last leg
I'm the last owner for the subar for
sure so I'm already modded it in several
ways that make it easier to live out of
and I'll I'll do videos on that at some
point later all right so so again the
starlink is late it everybody says that
it takes them forever to get it they
never actually come one person worst
story I read so far was they got pushed
out three months and they still didn't
get it um and you know So eventually
they just canel it um because of high
demand or whatever uh overwhelming ly
all the people
recommended uh trick to get the wire on
I would love to hear the trick yeah
write it in the chat we'll read it so um
a bunch of people have suggested in
different forums that the best way to
get the device which is what's holding
me up is to uh cancel it and buy it
through Lowe's or Best Buy and I went to
Best Buy the other day and I asked them
sure enough they have one it's just not
in stock because it's a high ticket item
so the way to do that is you you order
the high ticket item they bring it to
you the problem with that is according
to other people in the forums is that
that messes with your support agreement
because now you're getting support from
Best Buy uh or Lowe's and according to
one person I read the customer service
from starlink won't talk to them because
they bought it from a
retailer according to this person they
had to the starlink told them they had
to go to the retailer to get support on
the product
and that is that's not okay I mean
normally I would I would be okay with
that if it's a laptop or something but
if it's a starling thing and somebody
else said that they have had really good
experience or they've heard about people
having really good experience when they
buy direct it takes longer to get it
from starlink but when you have a
problem they're more likely to just send
you a new one because they own them and
when they have stock they're more likely
to just say oh hey here you go and give
you a new one so so
I'm going to go ahead and default to
buying directly from starlink because I
just have a feeling that I'm going to be
more likely to break it or or under
warranty or whatever and especially
since I'm going to be trying to haul it
around behind my bike and everything so
I I I want to I even though it's taking
longer uh I feel like having a support
ticket open with Starling might be a
better idea I don't know um and yeah so
mounting it through the trunk door
there's a there's is there a black black
pipe near the window
wiper uh I don't know I'll have to go
look maybe there is I'll have to go
check that out that's a I'll go check it
out for you Barney for next time so the
status is I'm
waiting and if it doesn't come before
July 4th uh July 3rd July 2nd or
something uh I'm going to do the road
trip anyway and I'm just going to use
Verizon so yesterday I spent a
significant amount of time my entire
Saturday uh getting rtmp streaming
from uh my uh from my bell box working
so this is a Mac this is this this video
is coming at you from a
Macintosh computer that's going that's
that's streaming through OBS to an
rtmp server that's running on my bell
box that's the same thing that I IRL
stream from all the time and then that
is streaming up to uh my normal my tower
in my room same one I stream from all
the time so the last night I
had uh Windows forced an upgrade so I'm
actually considering getting rid of
Windows on that computer and having
Linux on there instead and the reason
for that is purely
reliability I don't know I haven't quite
pulled the trigger on that yeah um so
that's not starlink related but I just
want to mention that so um actually
let's do another let's I'm going to do
another video about um RTL so let's
let's end this one now and then I'll do
another one really quick